<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on Clipper</title>
    <link>http://clipper.ai/overview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on Clipper</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 18:54:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://clipper.ai/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quickstart</title>
      <link>http://clipper.ai/overview/quickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 18:01:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://clipper.ai/overview/quickstart/</guid>
      <description>The easiest way to get started using Clipper is to install the clipper_admin pip package and use it interactively from a Python REPL. The Clipper admin contains the Clipper manager which can be used to start and manage a Clipper instance.
$ pip install clipper_admin $ python  Once you have the clipper_admin package installed, you can use it to start a Clipper instance and deploy your first model. When you use the Clipper manager to start a Clipper instance, it will run Clipper in Docker containers using Docker Compose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Classification Tutorial</title>
      <link>http://clipper.ai/overview/tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 19:16:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://clipper.ai/overview/tutorial/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial will walk you through the process of starting Clipper, creating an application, querying the application, and deploying models to improve application accuracy.
The tutorial uses the Clipper client management Python library for controlling Clipper. While this is the simplest way to manage Clipper, the client library is simply a convenience wrapper around a standardized management REST interface which can be queried with any REST client.
Setup The tutorial runs Clipper in Docker containers and orchestrates them with Docker-Compose, so you must have Docker and Docker-Compose installed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>